Bryan Leighton

Fullstack Web Developer

yan.leigh77@gmail.com	\geq
+49 151 6 874 6342	

bг

Tel Aviv, Israel

www.bryandl.com

linkedin.com/in/bryan77 **in**

github.com/bdlb77 🌎

I am a highly motivated person who has profound experience in work under extreme pressure, and great adaptability to any situation that is presented. Having served in a military that is not of my native tongue, while also learning medical terminology and techniques in a foreign language, I have learned that my strength is my ability to persevere through any hardship and realizing that nothing is ever impossible to accomplish.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

Freelance

10/2018 - Present

- Paul Ziemiak (CDU) Website WordPress
- SVApp Private Mentor and development of personal mobile app project.
- Priicer Automation of electricity meter based on price
- Immigration Works automation of Refugee hiring process in Germany

Instructor

Le Wagon Coding Bootcamp

07/2018 – Present Israel, Germany

- Instruct in fullstack web development

Contact: Clara Morgeneyer - +49 178 2004 525

Egoz Special Operations Unit Combat Medic Israel Defense Forces

11/2015 – 05/2018 Israel

- Special Operations Combat Medic First Sergeant
- Active Combat Medic on deployment in hostile zones
- Led First Aid and medical trainings within the Company

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development

Le Wagon Coding Bootcamp

04/2018 − 06/2018 Tel Aviv, Israel

HTML/ CSSRuby on RailsPostgreSQL

B.A. International Relations and Global Studies University of Texas at Austin

08/2012 - 05/2015 3.37/4.0

Middle Eastern Sudies
International Security

- French

Concentration in European Union studies

Sciences Po - Exchange

07/2013 - 12/2013

Paris, France

EU Strategic StudiesU.S. Foreign Policy

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Forget Me Not (06/2018 - 06/2018) 2

- 2-week final project during coding bootcamp. Business networking web app
- http://forgetmenot.network

Open Source Contributions

- NativeScript (https://docs.nativescript.org)

Immigration Works (02/2018 – Present)

- 3rd Place in Berlin Legal Tech Hackathon
- https://immigration-legaltech.herokuapp.com/

LEADERSHIP

Israel Defense Forces Special Operations Detachment

Company Medical Commander / Squad Commander

UT Austin Rugby (10/2014 - 05/2015)

Events and Activities Officer

UT Austin pro-Israel advocacy organization: Texans for Israel (09/2013 – 05/2014)

VP of programming and content

LANGUAGES

English Hebrew

Native or Bilingual Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

French German

Limited Working Proficiency Elementary Proficiency

INTERESTS

